Some things I want to call out that are
quite different than
>> [music]
>> a lot of web and full stack frameworks
that exist out there is Apple and
Android are fundamentally closed source
ecosystems. And this you can imagine
affects [music] how these foundation
models are trained.
So they just have less access to the
underlying code. I'm always going to do
something crazy that Apple, [music]
you know, may or may not think is a good
idea. So if you run into the limits
>> [music]
>> of their tool and of their capability,
does it allow you to get out of it to
fix it? I want to be able to access that
directly and so I try to get as close to
the underlying technology as possible.